Thank you for watching!
Morning Musume。 25th Anniversary Audition
You passed!
Good job.
Good afternoon.
Good morning~
Good morning.
by H.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Hello! Stee, this time with Rei Inoue from Juice=Juice and Akari Endo from Juice=Juice
We will be presenting this time with these two, so please bear with us until the end.
Juice! Juice! 10th Anniversary Concert Tour will be held next week on May 29th.
Juice! at Budokan.
It will be the first time in 3 months to see Juice!
I've never been able to forget the view of the penlights all over the Budokan that I saw at the last Budokan,
I'm really looking forward to seeing that view again, so I'm going to prepare and do my best so that I can grow up until then.
I will do my best too. I look forward to seeing it again.
And, at this Nippon Budokan concert, we will perform for the first time the new song "Pride Bright," which will be released on July 12.
This song has a lot of different choreography, so I would like each one of you to see it,
I think you will want to see more of it, so please pay attention to the dance, the song, and the melody.
I hope you will pay attention to the dance, the songs, and the melodies, and listen to them.
And now, JuiceJuice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour JuiceJuice, which started in March, has only one more show in Osaka on June 11.
It all happened so fast.
Do you think there is anything you have grown up from the tour so far?
Yes, in the last tour, I had to think about whether I would get the choreography right or not, and I had to keep trying to remember the song layouts in my head.
Oh, you have grown up, haven't you?
Yes.
Please look forward to the Nippon Budokan concert and the additional Osaka concert.
Please take a look at this video first. Please take a look.
Nippon Budokan Performance Video Production
All of them, including the Dokken Anno exhibition, are going to be very hard to get to.
Is that crazy?
Hey, you.
Don't be frightened.
You'll get swallowed up.
You'll be swallowed up
If you're gonna say that love is love
If you're going to say it's love
Be that way
Woo-hoo-hoo!
So manly
Confident
Like a man.
I'd like to be sweet on you, too.
But I'm in a position where I can't be sweet to you.
You'll notice my sign on your chest that says love, mercy and me.
Love me as much as anyone
Love me, love me, love me
Tomorrow, it'll be a dream or something mysterious like that
Embrace me, my naked feathers, as they were when I was born
Not your feathers, but your love is real
Kiss me
I don't want you to hate me. I don't know.
I want you to scold me when I'm wrong.
There are days when other people's boyfriends look better.
Pull on the colors and turn me around... with Sikari.
I want you to pull on my colors and turn me around... Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling and Circling
I know it's a lonely night, I know it's a lonely night, I know it's a crying night.
But tonight you're a little more soulful
I'm going to put on a little different perfume
I'm gonna put on a little different perfume.
Ah.
Love me, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me.
I love you, I love you, I love you so much
Not a little bit. A little bit of Goring.
It's just right
Hold me like I was born to be
Naked, naked, naked, naked kiss
Just think of this love as the real thing.
Just kiss me so I know that this love
I want you to kiss me so I know it's real.
Love me, love me, love me, love me
I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much.
And a little bit of force is just what I need
Hold me like I was born to be held
Naked, naked, naked, naked KISS
I just need to know that this love is real
Kiss me
Subtitles & Subtitles ENJOY
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching.
Akari Endo presents Halo! stay!
From here I would like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
So let's answer at a quick pace without thinking too much.
Here we go.
Akari Endo says she loves making nail tips.
What's your most confident work?
The ones with pink and white pearls.
It's been almost a year since you joined JuiceJuice.
What is your most memorable moment?
Going out for ice cream with my seniors.
New single to be released on July 12
What kind of Akari Endo do you think you could show?
A cool Akari Endo.
What do you want to do for next week's concert at Nippon Budokan?
I want to strengthen my abdominal muscles.I need to work on my abdominal muscles.
Hello! Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year!
What is the song that strikes a chord with Akari Endo right now?
Platonic Planet by JuiceJuice.
Wow! That's amazing! The tempo is really good!
It's so fast-paced!
So what you want to do before the Nippon Budokan concert is sit-ups?
Yes, when I was learning classical ballet
I used to have a pretty closed stomach when I was learning classical ballet.
But I don't have the opportunity to do sit-ups anymore.
I don't have the opportunity to do such abdominal muscles anymore
I would like to train my muscles again.
We do a lot of muscle training, don't we?
We do a lot of muscle training together in the dressing room.
Please come and join us!
Hello!
As this is the 25th anniversary of the Hello! Project's 25th anniversary.
Project's 25th anniversary, it was surprising that the song that strikes Akari right now
Platonic Planet.
I've loved Platonic Planet since before I joined the project.
Platonic Planet was my favorite song
I had been listening to it for a long time.
I've had the opportunity to play it on various occasions
I was very happy to be able to play it on various occasions.
So I chose it.
Well then, from now on...
When Akari is dancing to "Platonic Planet
I would like you to listen to the song while feeling how Akari is singing when she is dancing.
I'd like you to listen to it while feeling how Akari is singing.
Questions for Ms. Inoue will be asked after the VTR.
After the VTR, I asked Ms. Inoue a question about "Halo! Ste!
Beloved, we are brave and mighty
In the first place, the earth is the law of the jungle
Angulum, Ai no Kedamono, June 14, Onsai Ion
Beyonds New Single Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler
Now on sale
Untainted Night Sky Watches Over You
Beyonds New Single
Yume to nakuyona no yozora ha yoru hiragana ni Now on sale
How was it?
It was fun!
It was so much fun!
Wow!
It was so hot and I could feel everyone's passion,
Standing at the Budokan, I realized once again that there are people who love Beyonds so much,
It was a wonderful day.
It was a wonderful day for me.
Thank you very much.
I felt like I found something new as Beyonds,
I felt once again that I am supported by many people,
I hope to live up to the expectations of those people even more,
I would like to do my best to live up to their expectations and to grow with Beyonds.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
This is Beyonds.
What kind of juice do you think you were able to bring out in your new single released on July 12?
Cenobi.
Inoue-san, what are your problems during the rainy season?
That I get song notes.
Which Hello Project song with an attractive rhythm would you choose?
Come with me by Kobushi Factory
Come with me by Kobushi Factory!
Yay!
What kind of juice do you think you got out of the new single? I was asked "What kind of juice juice do you think we could have produced?
You said "Senobi".
This is...
Well, the age range of the Juice Juice team is pretty wide.
The older team sang in a more relaxed way, which was also good.
The younger team is a little bit taller than the older team, which I thought was cute.
This new single has a lot of different charms.
Oh!
I thought so too.
That's what I meant.
I'm Masashi Natsuyaki.
I'm Ilin Lisa from JuiceJuice.
I will continue to do my best.
Now, teacher, what would you like to make this time?
Yes, I am. Today I would like to make Kawahara soba.
Wow, I'm looking forward to it.
This is the first time I've heard of it.
I looked it up when I found out we were going to make this.
So, is it okay if I put it down?
Yes, it is.
I guess flavor is important.
What shall we start with this time?
Yes. Now it's time to boil the soba noodles.
The main dish.
Here comes the main dish.
It says that the soba noodles we prepared today should be boiled for 5 minutes,
But if you boil it for 5 minutes, it will become too soft,
And also, it will be cooked on the hot plate at the end of cooking,
So I think 4 minutes is fine.
Zbanban?
You can do it with a quick twist of the tongue.
Let's go with "Z-Bang-Bang".
Oh, wow!
Yabu.
What is "Z-Bam-Bam"?
But Z-Bang-Bang is good.
It's important.It's important.
Would you like me to boil it for you?
Yes.
It's hard to tell because the boiling water is bubbling,
But you can also smell the tea here, right?
Yes, it does. Yes, it does. The aroma of tea.
You can't throw this away either.
I know. I know.
I'll save it before I flush some of it.
I see. First.
But you often drink soba-yu?
Oh, soba-yu.
It comes out at the end, doesn't it?
I dare say it is similar, isn't it?
It's a little green and blue.
Yes, it is. It's finished boiling.
I lightly rinse it once with water.
I'm going to wash it quickly.
Put it here and wait a little bit.
I'll wait a little bit.
We want to drain off a little bit of water.
Here is the Miyamizu point!
Toss the boiled soba with oil.
Please teach me how to do this.
If you leave them as they are, they will stick together before you serve them.
The water is going to run off.
And since we cook them on a hot plate, they need to be crispy when they are cooked.
It's difficult.
I mix them well.
It's more like loosening.
Loosen it up. Like this.
That's right. A little bit on top.
Yes. All over.
It's all right now.
Yes.
Next time notice
Next, we will prepare condiments and dipping sauce.
Almost there. It's getting close to completion.
I prepared all-purpose green onion today.
There is no specific quantity or amount for this, but quite a bit more. If you like leeks, use a lot.
The tips are all the way on the cutting board.
In front. Yes, yes, yes.
A little more firmly down. Maybe I just put it on. Maybe I just did.
How do you like it, doctor? It's getting better.
Oh, it's getting better. Is it getting better?
It's growing fast, isn't it? You're young, you know.
You swallow quickly.
Yes, thank you very much. They cut me plenty.
Yes, now I would like to continue. Next, we will cut the lemon.
I think it should be pleasantly thick. Starting from the tip.
Yes, yes, yes. Yum, yum, yum.
Next, let's start preparing the dipping sauce.
Today, I'm going to eat it cold as it is.
The one that says "straight" on it. Straight.
I think of eating it with a little bit of tsuyu, rather than eating it with a lot of tsuyu.
Straight, plus this.
I kept it in a fussy way. The flavor of the meat comes out here.
First, this.
It depends on the bowl, but for one serving, about 100 is enough.
For two servings, it should be about 200.
If you have it.
If you put all of this in at once, it will be too salty.
About half.
Put about half of it in.
Put one of these in.
Put a third of this in.
This is 50 cc.
The three things I just mentioned.
The base is there, and then you taste it.
Adjust the thickness to your liking.
When you taste it, make sure it is warm before tasting it.
The best thing to do is to put a little bit of noodle on it and taste it.
If you think it is too salty and add water to make it thinner, it will not taste at all when you eat it.
If you think it is too salty and add water to thin it out, you won't be able to taste it when you eat it.
It's all over, isn't it?
It's better if it's thicker than you think.
It's a little bit salty.
You can also add lemon.
That's where the condiments really come into play.
Even if it's not too hot, the noodles themselves get warm on the hot plate.
That's right. We cook the noodles, too.
First of all, let's start with just this.
Take a taste of the dashi broth.
It's quite thick.
Thick?
It seems thick, but...
Is it too thin?
I'd like to make it thinner.
That's a lot.
It went in pretty well.
I got a lot in.
It's still adjustable.
Try one.
Just a little bit.
Put soba noodles on and taste it.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Now it's time to start the final stage of serving, right?
All of it!
Sound good! What do you think?
It's good, it's good, it's good.Nice, nice, nice.
Great volume!
The volume is amazing!
That's great!
Let's start from the left.
Let's see how you do it.
They really line up nicely, just like a pattern.
How fun is that?
It's fun.
It's easy to do with your hands.
It's easy because it's done with your hands.
You put the lemon on top of the meat.
It's nice and cool.
And let's put some grated maple on top.
What do you think?
It's good, isn't it?
Let's drink it just before eating. It's done!
Kawahara soba is ready.
What do you think? How do you like it, Airie?
It's very hearty, and I love eggs, green onions, meat, lemon, and soba,
It's a collection of all the things I love,
I'm looking forward to eating it.
It's good.
I did my best to make it as soon as possible, and I hope you'll try it.
Please cook lemon and grated momiji and sprinkle nori on it.
Bon appétit.
Yum.
Mmm.
I'm doing a crazy good job with the condiments.
Nice job on the condiments.
It's the best.
Green onion?
It's green onion.
That soba noodles...
If you eat it alone, it's quite salty.
But the meat is sweet.
But the meat is sweet, so it's perfect.
I see... the sweetness of the meat
And the nori and the seaweed are wonderful.
It has that lemon in it, so it's
It's amazingly refreshing.
Oh!
Hey, how would you like to try this again?
I'd love to try it.
I have a big hot plate at home.
I have a big hot plate at home, so we can do it again as a family.
It's not too hard to find the ingredients.
I'll get the ingredients and make it again.
I'll post it on my blog!
I declared it.
If I declare it, will it be okay?
I'm going to look for soba noodles first.
Yes, you're right.
It may be hard to find.
I'll make it a little crunchier.
I'd like to try it myself.
That's all for now, Ilaria!
Thank you again, doctor.
Thank you very much.
That's all for Hello Kitchen!
It's a great learning experience!
I personally don't cook much.
I've been saying that I want to do something, but
I've been saying that I want to do something, but I haven't been able to do it.
I'd like to make sweets for Valentine's Day, for example.
I'm very particular about making homemade sweets for Valentine's Day and other occasions.
I always make them at that time.
The other day, I made a large cup of sweets.
I made various layers like a parfait.
I made various kinds of sweets in a large cup.
It was delicious!
Thank you! I'm glad.
When I think about what I want to make
I think of sweets rather than food.
in my head.
Someday.
I don't know when that someday will come.
I hope I can become an adult woman who can also cook.
I was watching this VTR in the hope that I can become an adult woman who can cook.
So...
Do you cook, Akari Endo?
I don't cook at all.
But there are some foods that I would like to cook.
I want to make omelette rice, curry rice and stew.
All of them are home-style dishes, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
It's also a food I like a lot.
It would be fun to make them myself.
That's true. That's why I like it.
That's why you're so particular about what you do.
I'm sure you can make something really delicious.
I want to make it!
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope I'll be able to eat it too!
Hallo! Ste!
As I mentioned at the opening
Next week on May 29th
JuiceJuice 10th Anniversary Concert TourJuiceJuice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour
JuiceJuice at Budokan will be held
In honor of the show
We have selected some of the most impressive performances we have seen or performed at
We would like to introduce some of the most impressive performances
I'd like to introduce you to some of the performances we've seen and performed at the Budokan.
I'll start from the top!
The performance of Ms. Yoshikazu Miyamoto's graduation
It left a deep impression on me.
During the rehearsal
It was my first performance as JuiceJuice
It was the first time for me to perform at Nippon Budokan as JuiceJuice.
I was really nervous.
I didn't know what to do at all.
but we performed many, many songs as only a new member can.
There were many songs that only a new member can learn.
There were many songs to learn that only a new member can do.
And as I communicated with my seniors
I think we became very close to each other.
I also thought that Miyamoto-san's graduation dress was very beautiful.
Her dress was so beautiful.
The backs of the graduates are so strong.
I admire them so much.
I admired them so much.
It was rare for me to be in a position to see them off up close.
It left a deep impression on me.
I was also a member of Morning Musume。 22's
Kagawa Kayade's graduation performance
Kagawa's graduation performance was very memorable.
Kagawa's dance was really wonderful and her singing voice was also wonderful.
Her singing voice was also very beautiful.
I was really absorbed in the performance.
It was so wonderful.
Rio Sakurai, who is in the same class with me
Rio Sakurai, who is a colleague of mine, told me about her first time at the Budokan
I was looking for a place to tell her after the show.
I was also looking for places to tell her afterwards.
There were so many things to see at the show.
I think it was a performance with many highlights and it left a deep impression on me.
In my opinion, the entrance of "Brand New Morning" was the best.
I still remember the beginning of "Brand New Morning" very well.
I still remember it very much
I still remember it and feel a little bit moved.
I feel the same emotion as all the fans
I feel the same emotion as all the fans.
We are also preparing for the Nippon Budokan
Nippon Budokan on May 29th.
I hope you will have abs!
Even if you don't.
We need to work out.
It's important to have a good core.
I want to work out so that we can all give a great performance.
I'll do my best.
[Music]
Now, let's hear your voices along with the castanets!
Beyonds, you're hot!
With the voice of castanets!
Twist, twist, twist!
Twit-twit-twit!
Twitwitwit!
Twitwitwitwit!
me
rar
I can't help it
Young Papple who just wants to hang out
I can't help it!
Mystery novels about natural disasters
I can't help myself
Your version of riding ahead of the times
I can't help it
I keep putting words together
I keep adding melodies
I'm always in the mood
You'll get a batch of soliloquies
Don't sing the latest songs alone
People who have no place to pull
Ha-ha-ha!
Rikuo!
Hot summer is coming
Shoboshon on our side
It's coming up higher and higher
Happy beats from the body's stupidity
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Jump!
Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump
The hot walls are in the way
I'm gonna break your shaky heart, I'm gonna break your shaky heart
If you're home alone and lonely
That's even better
Jump!
We're gonna have a hot festival tonight
We're all in this together
ZOIZOI
One more time.
ZOIZOIZOI
Touching all those hands and all those lids
So if it's a country, surely it's a conversation orSo I'm sure the country would be a great place for conversation and
ZOIZOIZOI
Idol world is Piras now.
ZOIZOIZO.
Oh, I got carried away. I got carried away.
ZOIZOIZOIZO.
I don't know why I can't listen to it alone with my mucous membranes
I can't stop the tears, my eyelids are getting uneasy
If you talk to someone, you'll lose the blurriness in your heart
Summer's coming in hot and everyone's spirits are gently rising
Just right, just right tempo, just right tempo, just right tempo, just right tempo, just right tempo, just right tempo.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
We've got a lot of faith in you, and you've got a lot of faith in us.
We'll talk to each other about our summer sense of mind
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Shed some hot tears tonight
Ah... 2!
It's not uncommon for a person to have a parched throat the next day after speaking out too loud for a long time like this.
It happens. It's hot. It's hot.
And it's nice to take a break from standing around like this, because you'll be tired all the time after a long time.
But here's the last promise. This song is made to be the most exciting after this.
Three years of power for the last chorus. Here we go.
Summer's coming in hot and everyone's spirits are gently rising
Let the upbeat carry you away, let's go fly
The hot wind is in the way, I'm gonna break your shaky heart
If you're at home all alone, come on over
♪ Tonight's the night we're gonna make it hot
We're gonna make it a hot festival
Thank you for watching.
That's what Japan's doing right now
It's my time
It's not over yet!
Ta-da!
I love you just as much as you love me
I love you with my voice, with my heart, with my shouts, with everything
Voices, hearts, screams, everything
Young man, hang in there.
♪ More than irresponsible
You don't even know what we're going through right now
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
We'll never know what it's like to be shackled
I wonder what kind of chains
I'll grab it and tear it off
Did you think I was a cat?
The one with the dyed hair?
And that girl who's so helpless
What's in your heart?
Me, me, me, me, me
This is what I'm looking for.
You can't win today and you can't win now.
Ready?
Why do you sigh?
Why do you yearn?
At the bottom of a night of tears
Why are you unraveling your fingernails?
Look at the stars behind me, it's my turn to fight
So, precious, I don't want to lose, Guy Guidance
I didn't protect my dream
Nobody's here to eat, nobody's here to believe.
All that pie pie for you.
Let me know, let me know, look, let me know
You'll win the war, but you'll lose the war.
You win once. Come on, one. What do you want?
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
I'm in the middle of the line of sight
Let's sing, Mr. Treasure
Shout more on the radio
I want to be, I want to be
I don't know my limits
Shall we find me?
Yeah, it's nighttime.
What are you living for?
Why do you long for it?
If you hold on to your name...
If you hold on to it.
I want to give you what you want.
I can't wait to see what comes out the other side
It's my time
I'm about to let it take over
Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump!
I want you to love your true self
♪ I want to love you for who you really are ♪
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
I wanna do this, I wanna do that, I wanna do that, I wanna do that
I want to do this, I want to do that, I want to do this, I want to do this, I want to do this
I'm gonna show you the real me, I'm gonna show you the real me, I'm gonna show you the real me
Don't let go of my hand
I'm gonna make your heart sparkle, sparkle, sparkle
I want to do this, I want to do that, I want to do this, infinite power
I'm gonna show you my hands
I won't let go
I'll never let go of your hand, I'll never let go of your hand
It's my time
I'm gonna leave it to you.
Jump!
I want you to love your true self
Let your voice, your heart, your mind ring
Let's give it to begin
Time to go
Time to goGo!
We're almost there! Fight!
Juice-Juice's inomerate, Akari Endo, is presenting "Halo! Stay!
It's time to say goodbye. Here is an announcement.
Juice-Juice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour Juice!
Yay!
I hope I can show you a more matured Juice-Juice at the Budokan after 3 months.
I will do my best!
Juice-Juice's new single will be released on July 12.
It is a double A-side single including "Pride Bright".
It is a single with cool Akari Endo and tallness as the key point.
Please listen to it a lot.
And Hello! Project 2023 Spring City Circuit Juice!
Juice will be performing at Osaka NHK Hall on June 11, the last day of the event,
Juice will be performing at Osaka NHK Hall on June 11, the last day of the event, so I hope we can show you the culmination of Juice!
And on June 3, we will be performing at Poppin' Base in Kyoto 2023.
It's not often that we get a chance to talk with other idols,
I hope to see many idols and absorb what they have to say,
Juice!
Please look forward to it.
Juice! Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
Project members. New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time, I am joined by Juice-Juice Innovator, Akari Endo.
Goodbye!
Please subscribe to our channel.